solidseovps.com 2019-01-15

# Privacy Policy - Our policy regarding your privacy

In an effort to protect our clients' and site visitors privacy and rights, Solid has established a Privacy Policy which explains what information we gather on visitors & what we do with information that we gather.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which SolidSeoVps.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a "User").

You may have already heard about the new European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). In order to comply with the new GDPR standard, we've updated our Privacy Policy

We aim to make sure that your personal information is handled with care and processed securely. We encourage you to take the time to review our revised Privacy Policy.

We cares about your privacy. For this reason, we collect and use personal data only as it might be needed for us to deliver to you our world-class products, services, websites and mobile applications (collectively, our “Services”). Your personal data includes information such as:

**Name**

**Address**

**Telephone number**

**Date of birth**

**Email Address**

**Other data collected that could directly or indirectly identify you.**

Our Privacy Policy is intended to describe to you how and what data we collect, and how and why we use your personal data. It also describes options we provide for you to access, update or otherwise take control of your personal data that we process.

We collect information so that we can provide the best possible experience when you utilize our Services. Much of what you likely consider personal data is collected directly from you when you:

(1) create an account or purchase any of our Services (ex: billing information, including name, address, credit card number, government identification);

(2) request assistance from our heroic customer support team (email address); 

(3) complete contact forms or request newsletters or other information from us (ex: email); or

(4) participate in contests and surveys, apply for a job, or otherwise participate in activities we promote that might require information about you. 

However, we also collect additional information when delivering our Services to you to ensure necessary and optimal performance. These methods of collection may not be as obvious to you, so we wanted to highlight and explain below a bit more about what these might be (as they vary from time to time) and how they work:

**Account related information** is collected in association with your use of our Services, such as account number, purchases, when products renew or expire, information requests, and customer service requests and notes or details explaining what you asked for and how we responded.

**Cookies and similar technologies** on our websites and our mobile applications allow us to track your browsing behavior, links clicked, items purchased, your device type, and to collect various data, including analytics, about how you use and interact with our Services. This allows us to provide you with more relevant product offerings, a better experience on our sites and mobile applications, and to collect, analyze and improve the performance of our Services. We may also collect your location (IP address) so that we can personalize our Services. For additional information, and to learn how to manage the technologies we utilize.

**Data about Usage of Services** is automatically collected when you use and interact with our Services, including metadata, log files, cookie/device IDs and location information. This information includes specific data about your interactions with the features, content and links (including those of third-parties, such as social media plugins) contained within the Services, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type and settings, the date and time the Services were used, information about browser configuration and plugins, language preferences and cookie data, information about devices accessing the Services, including type of device, what operating system is used, device settings, application IDs, unique device identifiers and error data, and some of this data collected might be capable of and be used to approximate your location. 

**Supplemented Data** may be received about you from other sources, including publicly available databases or third parties from whom we have purchased data, in which case we may combine this data with information we already have about you so that we can update, expand and analyze the accuracy of our records, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you. If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

We strongly believe in both minimizing the data we collect and limiting its use and purpose to only that (1) for which we have been given permission, (2) as necessary to deliver the Services you purchase or interact with, or (3) as we might be required or permitted for legal compliance or other lawful purposes. These uses include:

**Delivering, improving, updating and enhancing the Services we provide to you.** We collect various information relating to your purchase, use and/or interactions with our Services. We utilize this information to:

\- Improve and optimize the operation and performance of our Services 

\- Diagnose problems with and identify any security risks, errors, or needed enhancements to the Services

\- Detect and prevent fraud and abuse of our Services and systems

\- Collecting aggregate statistics about use of the Services

\- Understand and analyze how you use our Services and what products and services are most relevant to you.

Often, much of the data collected is aggregated or statistical data about how individuals use our Services, and is not linked to any personal data, but to the extent it is itself personal data, or is linked or linkable to personal data, we treat it accordingly. 

**Sharing with trusted third parties.** We may share your personal data with affiliated companies within our corporate family, with third parties with which we have partnered to allow you to integrate their services into our own Services, and with trusted third party service providers as necessary for them to perform services on our behalf, such as:

\- Processing credit card payments

\- Serving advertisements

\- Conducting contests or surveys

\- Performing analysis of our Services and customers demographics

\- Communicating with you, such as by way email or survey delivery

\- Customer relationship management.

We only share your personal data as necessary for any third party to provide the services as requested or as needed on our behalf. These third parties (and any subcontractors) are subject to strict data processing terms and conditions and are prohibited from utilizing, sharing or retaining your personal data for any purpose other than as they have been specifically contracted for (or without your consent).

**Communicating with you.** We may contact you directly or through a third party service provider regarding products or services you have signed up or purchased from us, such as necessary to deliver transactional or service related communications. We may also contact you with offers for additional services we think you’ll find valuable if you give us consent, or where allowed based upon legitimate interests. You don’t need to provide consent as a condition to purchase our goods or services. These contacts may include:

\- Email

\- Automated phone calls or text messages.

**Compliance with legal, regulatory and law enforcement requests.** We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (such as subpoena requests), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.

To the extent we are legally permitted to do so, we will take reasonable steps to notify you in the event that we are required to provide your personal information to third parties as part of legal process. We will also share your information to the extent necessary to comply with ICANN or any ccTLD rules, regulations and policies when you register a domain name with us.

Solid Systems LLC may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site "Solidseovps.com" to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Solid Systems LLC and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with Solid Systems and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. At no time will Solid Systems's database of users ever be sold to any entity for the purpose of marketing or mailing lists. Personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to our business partners without your prior consent, except that we will disclose the information we collect to third parties when, in our good faith judgment, we are obligated to do so under applicable laws

Solid Systems LLC collects personally identifiable information from Users through online forms for ordering products and services. We may also collect information about how Users use our Web site "Solidseovps.com", for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site.

**Website analytics.** We use multiple web analytics tools provided by service partners such as Google Analytics, MixPanel and Singular to collect information about how you interact with our website or mobile applications, including what pages you visit, what site you visited prior to visiting our website, how much time you spend on each page, what operating system and web browser you use and network and IP information. We use the information provided by these tools to improve our Services. These tools place persistent cookies in your browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our website. Each cookie cannot be used by anyone other than the service provider (ex: Google for Google Analytics). The information collected from the cookie may be transmitted to and stored by these service partners on servers in a country other than the country in which you reside. Though information collected does not include personal data such as name, address, billing information, etc., the information collected is used and shared by these service providers in accordance with their individual privacy policies. 

### Account Closure and Data Deletion

You may request to close your account. The following conditions apply:

\- All products and services must be cancelled prior to closure. If there are any active products or services in the account, the account cannot be closed.

\- All In Store Credits will be forfeited.

\- You will no longer be able to log into your account after it is closed.

\- Upon closing your account, it may take up to 2 days for account data to be deleted. After deletion, you will no longer be able to access your account and your account will be unrecoverable. Data that is necessary for the products or services you have purchased may be retained if it is required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements.

1- You can at anytime contact us by[ Submitting a Ticket](https://www.solidseovps.com/submitticket.php?step=2&deptid=2), to delete your account and/or your data stored on our clouds

2- You can at anytime contact us by[ Submitting a Ticket](https://www.solidseovps.com/submitticket.php?step=2&deptid=2) to delete your account and all personal data on cloud will be also deleted. You have the rights to delete your account and personal data at any time.

3- A data protection officer (DPO) is assigned with our billing department 24/7 contact billing [at] solidseovps.com or can be reached by [ Submitting a Ticket](https://www.solidseovps.com/submitticket.php?step=2&deptid=2)

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by accessing your account client area on our website, under "Edit Account". We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Solid Systems LLC reserves the right to update and amend this policy as it is deemed necessary or appropriate to do so. We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how Solid Systems LLC is protecting your information.**
